HUGO MOYA AGÜERO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

MAIN PROJECTS

POKÉDEX



August 2023

An application where the user enters his name in an input and can filter the content either by type or by pokemon name.

- Developed with ReactJS and CSS.
- Redux library, global states and react dom router.

Technical achievement:

The application was built in 72 hours using ReactJS.

USER CRUD



July 2023

Application where there are created, read, updated, and deleted

- Developed with ReactJS and CSS.
- A useFetch is done with all the functionality of Get, Post, Delete, and Update.

Technical achievement:

Construction in 72 hours of a CRUD with ReactJS.

RICK AND MORTY APP



July 2023

Application of the characters from the Rick and Morty series, with a bar search to filter them based on parallel universe numbers.

- Developed with ReactJS and CSS.
- In the process an API is consumed using useState, useEffect and Axios.

Technical achievement:

Construction in 72 hours of an application with ReactJS.

CONTACT



+506-8742-8647



hugoma019@gmail.com



Costa Rica

SUMMARY

Hello, I'm a frontend developer with a passion for creating beautiful and user-friendly web experiences.

I specialize in crafting responsive and interactive web applications using the latest technologies.

I am dedicated to delivering high-quality code and designs that enhance user engagement and

SKILLS

HTML

satisfaction.

- JavaScript
- CSS
- ReactJS
- Power BI
- Excel
- Web Design
- Problem-Solving

EXPERIENCE

SR. PRODUCT SAFETY AND COMPLIANCE ASSOCIATE

Amazon

December 2022 - July 2023

- Classify products based on the potential risk of each one, for proper storage and safe transportation.
- Identify and remove from the website products that violate Amazon's policies regarding restricted products.

Softskill achievement:

Teamwork.

GO-AI ASSOCIATE

Amazon

May 2020 - December 2022

 Observe videos of the storage of products by Amazon employees and through software, mark the location of the product to keep inventory updated.

Softskill achievement:

Attention to detail.

EDUCATION

2023

ACADEMLO

Foundations in HTML, CSS and Javascript

Front-End Development with React

2020

PXS SCHOOL OF EXCELLENCE

Certified Six Sigma Yellow Belt

2020 - 2021

INSTITUTO TECNOLÓGICO DE COSTA RICA (TEC)

Quality Technician

2011 - 2014

UNIVERSIDAD METROPOLITANA CASTRO CARAZO

Bachelor degree, Industrial Engineering